Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
To my friend.
Giovanni Fiore Coltellacci
Evening. Arms up.
Pocket.
All good. Elyas?
Take a seat.
You're a hard man to find.
This thing still work?
I've got a job for you.
Pays very well.
A security firm needs muscle
to protect a Middle East family
renting a vacation chateau.
A guy like you would reassure them.
And who's "a guy like me"?
Listen. Elyas.
You're like a brother to me.
I want to help.
I'm just looking out for you.
I'm working on something right now.
You've got a knife now?
And this here?
And this... For your neighbor?
And this?
- My aunt. in Morocco.
- Right.
"Your aunt."
- Care to explain?
- It's Miroslav.
I don't know what he's up to.
He talks all night long.
I've noted all his movements.
- Last night. he...
- Wait.
- Last night?
- Yeah.
You're not taking your meds.
Miroslav left a week ago.
I heard him last night...
I'm telling you.
Miroslav left here a week ago!
You have a duty of care.
We had an agreement.
Elyas...
You need help.
An ambulance will pick you up.
Elyas!
ST. FRANCIS OF ASSISI SHELTER HOUSE
- That yours?
- What do you think?
Everyone wants to fly.
- Thought it over?
- What's the catch?
There's no catch.
I know this security firm.
so just trust me.
Here.
Everything you need.
You start tomorrow.
The phone is a gift.
You really deserve this fresh start.
Believe me.
Yes ?
Elyas Florès.
Show your ID to the camera behind you.
Mr. Jamal Al-Kuwari.
- Good day. sir.
- Good day.
Your name?
Elyas... Florès.
Okay.
Where are my earrings?
They were just here!
You must've seen them!
- I didn't...
- Amina!
Don't worry. They'll find them.
Come here.
- Your new bodyguard.
- Good day. ma'am.
Nour!
What?
Come here.
Take off your sunglasses.
Say hello to Mr. Florès.
Hello. Nour.
I'm the new guard.
Given your accent. we'll speak French.
Or English. but I'd be surprised
a yokel like you speaks it.
Nour!
Be polite. Don't act like a brat.
Now... Say hello to him.
Politely.
Salam. mister.
Good enough?
I'll show you to your room.
Watch what you say here.
Lebanese mother. Her French is perfect.
She's already fired three guards.
And the girl's a real pain.
- Can I have my gun?
- No.
Al-Kuwari ordered to keep them
locked in the control room.
Our rooms are here.
That one's yours.
Here.
The password to the camera network.
Noah will install the app on your phone.
Left. to the pool.
There are cameras across the chateau.
They're all on your phone.
No cameras in bedrooms.
Only in the upstairs corridors.
But you'll never go up there.
Only Brabus has access.
- Got it?
- Affirmative.
Open the door.
Now you've reached the pool.
Your chair. on the left.
You don't move unless we say so.
As of now.
wherever Mrs. Al-Kuwarigoes. you go.
Find my earrings?
Brabus to Team.
Status on Ma'am. Nour. Estate.
Elyas to Brabus. Ma'am in sight.
Francis to Team.
Heading out with Mr. Al-Kuwari.
You.
Come with me.
You'll keep her company.
I'll eat later.
Your tie.
You work for me. right? So sit.
Are you dumb or something?
What's that? A knife?
Fishing knife.
What's a fishing knife for?
Undoing knots.
- Knots where?
- In a parachute.
Or in fishing nets.
You used to be a fisherman?
You eat this?
I don't like it when innocents suffer.
Boomer!
Yeah. good Boomer!
Good boy!
Yes. Boomer!
There you go!
Yes!
Know the other guards?
- No. why?
- They're shady.
Why say that?
They've stolen jewelry.
Diamond earrings.
Now they'll take action.
Elyas. please. stay calm.
Don't get involved.
Why say that?
If something goes down. call the cops.
You're not in the army now. okay?
Francis to Team.
Returning with Mr. Al-Kuwari.
Elyas. Delivery. north entrance.
Be right there. over.
Thanks. have a nice day.
Nour...
Nour!
I just wanted to see
what it's like outside.
You're in for the punishment
of a lifetime!
It's the new guard's fault!
He made me go outside to test my bike!
Is that true?
She must never go outside.
Not her. not Amina.
Is that clear?
Yes. sir.
Nour!
Back to your posts.
Elyas. come with me.
The brat got away from you. eh?
- We need to be on the lookout.
- I'm listening.
Two guys waiting on a bike.
The passenger was armed. Ready to fire.
When Al-Kuwari leaves. they'll strike.
- Are you sure?
- Certain.
We need to be armed.
Let me have a cigarette.
It's fine. I've smoked before.
Hey. look. Right there.
That constellation is Cygnus.
That's not Cygnus.
- Why lie? How would you know?
- That's Hercules.
That's Cygnus.
Oh. right...
Yeah. you're right.
How do you know about stars?
Not to be mean. but...
You don't talk. you don't laugh...
You don't even smile.
You just stand there
giving people the stink eye.
But you know about stars?
Come on.
Why do you know about stars?
- My old job.
- When you'd go out to sea?
No. I wasn't a fisherman.
I was a parachutist. in the army.
I'd do night jumps. from 33.000 feet.
Up there. you see the stars up close.
Wow.
You'd parachute?
I could never do that.
I'm too scared of heights.
Have you killed people?
You know...
Where I used to live.
from my dad's palace.
I could see the stars super well.
A palace. really?
Yeah. a palace.
But I was never allowed out. so...
A bit like here.
Did you know my mother was a princess?
And my dad is...
Hey! You don't sleep much. do you?
Elyas...
Your cigarettes.
The Hercules constellation...
You have everything here.
I want to go out shopping.
So Nour can go outside.
I want to eat out.
do what everyone else does!
But we're not like everyone else!
You know this. Amina!
I know.
Just buy out the stores
and the bodyguard can come with us.
We'll go crazy in here.
Just look at Nour.
She's hiding herself away.
- What do you think she'll do next time?
- Mom's right.
We were locked away back home.
It's the same here.
- Nour...
- Let us go out for once.
Just once!
Nour. go to your room.
The adults are talking. Go!
I'm 13!
I'm not a kid anymore.
And you're a selfish jerk! Just like...
Just like the other guy!
Right... Okay.
Write me up a list of all the stores.
I'll see what I can do.
You. take Francis as your driver.
I don't need him.
- Why?
- He isn't driver certified.
If it's just me. it's more discreet.
Okay. fine.
Hey. take it easy!
Why bring up Francis' clearance?
The others think you're up to something.
Take a look at this.
We checked the outside cameras.
No motorbike. just the street.
Camera A. you and Nour.
Camera B. Nour and you.
Cam C. the same.
No motorbike.
And what's this?
You're not allowed upstairs.
You went there day one!
You scoping the place out?
I'm warning you. Elyas.
Don't get any ideas.
Give me your gun. Now.
Fine. I'll show Al-Kuwari.
All right! Now. Louis Vuitton.
No. not Louis Vuitton!
Enough stores already!
Why do I have a daughter
who doesn't care about fashion?
Fine!
Put yourself in my shoes.
I've really missed this!
Check out that car!
Whoa! Bro. sick ride!
What car is this? Must be a big-shot!
Whoa. he's got a piece! Move it!
Buckle up.
- What's going on?
- Buckle up!
It's them! It's them!
- Who are they?
- They've found us!
Watch out!
To your rooms. quick!
- Now hold on...
- You're in on this!
What? What happened?
You know.
Who was that?
Your mom said. "They found us."
Who found you?
Nour.
I can show you. if you like.
This is where I used to live.
But my mom and I
had to leave. because...
My dad wanted to marry me off.
This man...
was 50 years old.
- Jamal wants to marry you off?
- Jamal isn't my dad. He's my uncle.
He and my dad hate each other.
And Jamal saved us.
He said France would help us.
Who is your father?
My dad is Sheikh Abdul El Saïd.
He has six wives and 18 children.
He arranges all the marriages.
If he finds me...
I'm done for.
Elyas!
Nour. are you ready?
I told him. Mom.
Jamal wants to leave now.
- But my telescope...
- I'll buy you another one.
What's wrong?
Okay. got it.
Very good. go ahead.
- We'll be ready in an hour.
- Ready for what?
Why didn't you tell me about her father?
About how she escaped?
She wasn't supposed to tell you.
Why didn't you tell me the truth?
You've been playing me from the start.
It's not your problem!
It doesn't matter. we're leaving.
The French authorities
have initiated a protocol.
What are you scheming with Brabus?
The same as you.
You'll be handsomely compensated.
Liar!
Confirm your position.
This is Blue 1.
East sector clear.
No sign of target.
Woman sighted. Entering sports hall.
West. Green 2 en route.
- Nour?
- I don't know.
- Come on.
- We were heading for the car...
Red 2. over. I have the girl.
Ready for extraction.
- Red 2. confirm position.
- West. Pool.
Let's go.
Wait for me here.
Nour! That's Nour!
Hide here. I'll handle it.
Take this.
My darling!
What about Jamal?
Get down! Now!
Out.
- Leave the bags.
- We need them!
- You do as I say!
- Okay. but we keep the bags.
Wait here.
Come on.
Can you slow down. please?
Where do we go now?
Where do we go?
Hey there. Where's Nacho?
Beat it. Arab.
There's nothing for you here.
Tell him Elyas wants to see him.
So. you're back?
Sara...
I just want to speak to your father.
Nacho's dead.
You speak to me now.
What do you want?
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I just need somewhere to lay low.
Please. he needs a doctor.
I'm helping them.
Not you.
Come.
Are you a doctor?
Yeah. why?
Do you think gypsies
only know how to steal chickens?
Is it bad?
No.
The slug went through the muscle.
And this guy's a tough one.
- Don't recognize me?
- Of course I remember you.
Tamara.
Now I'm old. Now I'm "Tata."
Can you find more of these for me?
Are you really that bad?
That's how you say thank you?
I don't know any other way.
- Never would've thought he was a gypsy.
- His father was.
But he married a gadji.
A Moroccan woman.
He could've lived
with his aunt in Morocco...
But he wanted to stay here.
So Nacho. my father. adopted him.
He raised him like his own son.
Then why don't you
love him like a brother?
Dylan was my brother.
But Elyas got him involved in the army.
What the hell did you do?
The main suspect is Elyas Florès.
who worked security
for a rich Middle Eastern family.
A former commando.
he won the favor of Jamal Al-Kuwari
thanks to his exploits.
Diagnosed with psychosis.
Florès was discharged from the army
following an operation in Afghanistan.
Florès is suspected
of killing five individuals.
two members of household staff
and three guards he worked alongside.
He also stole jewelry
from the Al-Kuwari family
estimated to be worth
millions of euros...
Wherever you go. people die.
I want you gone!
You've got an hour to leave.
That's your plan? Pin it on me?
Elyas. let go of her!
If you touch her...
You're not well. Elyas.
Maybe you did it. maybe not.
I don't care!
Quit screwing around. right now!
What's got into you?
I've been calling all day!
On your bugged phone? I dumped it.
Did you recruit the hit squad?
What "hit squad"?
I shouldn't have cut you in.
I knew you'd flip. like in Afghanistan!
Why kill the guards? For money?
Stop! Stop!
Why did you kill Al-Kuwari?
Al-Kuwari?
Al-Kuwari? What are you talking about?
They all went back home.
The whole family.
The father. the mother. the girl!
It was on the news. Didn't you see?
Everything was wrecked.
They were shooting everywhere.
Al-Kuwari died here.
There was blood everywhere.
Now there's nothing.
There!
That saw everything.
That's what they showed on the news.
All three of them went back home.
But Al-Kuwari is dead.
Nobody killed him. He went home.
Look.
There was never any hit squad.
Boomer bit the commando who killed Noah.
He went down right there.
Boomer? Who's that?
- The dog.
- What dog?
I killed them all...
One by one.
Turn yourself in.
I don't remember anything.
Elyas!
Elyas. come see this.
Look.
See that?
You were right. The dog's there.
A commando killed your colleague.
It's a deepfake.
This outfit has deep pockets.
Copy it all onto this.
Why me?
Durante.
Who's that?
I helped him out.
His firm launders cash.
He noticed you
after seeing our army photos.
So when he needed
a reliable guy who spoke Arabic...
Fuck. Yann! What the hell is this?
- You fucked me over.
- What are you talking about?
Your pal here fucked everything up
when he went mad and killed my guys!
I've seen you before...
- The shisha bar.
- Yeah.
I was assessing you.
on his recommendation!
Why choose me?
Who am I to you? Why?
Don't want to tell me?
Who are these commandos?
Where are they from?
Pakistan? Yemen? Where?
What fucking commandos?
Yann. please... Make him stop.
Make him fucking stop!
Stop. stop. stop!
I'm listening.
When El Saïd found out...
That his brother-in-law was in France
with his wife and daughter...
He just lost it.
He had a commando unit sent in
to extract the girl and bring her home.
We handled the logistics
in order to create the deepfake.
A robbery gone wrong.
an ex-soldier with mental issues...
And I was the perfect fit.
That's right.
And the mother?
No. they only want the girl.
Who do you work for?
Listen... Next time. I'll blind you.
- They'll never stop...
- Who?
- Drop it. or you're a dead man.
- I want to know what's in this for you.
I reckon you're Homeland Security.
It doesn't matter. Just don't lie to me.
What are you looking at?
- Who's watching us?
- You'll see.
Check outside.
I'll ask you one last time.
Who are you working for?
Our outfit is strictly off-the-books.
It's a pyramid structure.
We only know
who's above us and who's below us.
When orders come in. we execute them.
Who gives the orders?
- We don't know who's in charge.
- Military?
I'm telling you. I don't know.
Why help El Saïd?
He threatened to pull
all his arms contracts with France.
We deliver the girl or we lose billions.
What do you expect?
This world's rotten to the core.
What's rotten is...
kidnapping a 13-year-old girl.
If things didn't work out here.
Jamal considered going to England.
No. ever since Brexit.
the borders have been too tight.
All of French intelligence is after you.
It was already serious
with Nour's father. but now...
Wait...
Our bags.
Look.
Cash.
Bonds. stocks. Bitcoin. crypto...
Nour has more in her bag. just in case.
And this too.
Fake IDs that Jamal got us.
- Do you want to see Nour's?
- No.
The issue is crossing borders
with your photos.
If a guard doesn't catch you.
then facial recognition software will.
Or you'd need to bribe customs.
How?
No customs. no checkpoints.
I've done it before.
We go through Calais.
Yeah...
Calais is our best option.
One of my clients smuggles migrants.
- It costs an arm and a leg.
- How much?
20.000. 25.000 euros...
Each.
That's nothing.
If you need a car...
Shall I call him?
Whoa. are you stupid?
Why'd you do that?
He's leaking our position.
Some rest would do you good.
Where are you going?
Is what they say about him true?
What happened in Afghanistan?
How am I meant to answer that?
Before. he used to be someone.
He was our big brother.
Our hero.
- My friend.
- You said. "was."
Who are you?
- I know it's you.
- What?
Get off him! Get off him!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Stop! Get off him!
- Where were you?
- You drive. No stopping till Calais.
I'll sleep a while.
You're gonna sleep? That's good news.
Her father is a tyrant.
There's nothing he wouldn't do.
To him. Nour is a bargaining chip.
Nour was depressed.
She wouldn't eat a thing.
She'd hide behind her telescope.
One day. I caught her up on the roof.
At the very top...
I thought she'd jump.
That's when I found the strength.
I managed to reach my brother.
He asked if I was ready
to risk it all. even our lives.
All to save Nour.
I didn't need to think twice.
He organized it in a few days.
- We escaped.
- You're very brave.
I don't know about that.
I did it so I could see her laugh again.
It's also thanks to you.
I don't want to leave.
Not without you.
If you ever need me one day.
I'll be there for you.
Swear it.
I swear.
- Thanks.
- Time to go.
I added a little extra.
to grease the wheels.
Wait here.
We can't screw this up. so hang back.
So?
He said for that much.
he'd smuggle your cousins too.
I'm not carrying cargo.
just delivering that truck to England.
Their scanners can't detect
this rear compartment.
I can't. I'm claustrophobic.
- It'll be all right.
- No. Elyas. it won't!
It'll be all right.
- What about fires?
- No fires.
- What if...
- Then I'll be there.
What? You're coming with us?
Okay.
I'll follow you on the A16.
until the Eurotunnel.
Contact me when you get there.
Come on.
Can you hold my bag?
- What was that?
- Nothing.
Just the truck starting.
Listen... We're accelerating.
We're on the highway.
CHANNEL TUNNEL
Where are we now?
Must be Customs.
Praise be to God!
- No!
- Nour!
Stop!
Mom!
Our unit set fire to the trailer.
Along with 15 refugees...
The driver...
The girl's mother...
And your buddy.
Except that the police
found the trailer...
With only 17 bodies inside.
Not 18.
One's missing.
So...
Where's Elyas Florès?
I wouldn't want to be in your shoes.
Because...
You can't imagine
the shit you're in now.
What don't we know. huh?
You messed with the wrong guy.
Dylan Torres. A gypsy.
Dylan Torres ? Who's that?
They were like brothers.
Of all the elite soldiers.
they were the best.
One day. in Afghanistan.
Dylan was captured by the Taliban.
Elyas went to get him back. alone.
He was out there for days.
He couldn't find him.
so he let himself get captured.
It took us a month
to find him and the Taliban.
When we found him...
he was being kept in a hole
no bigger than a grave.
with Dylan's severed head for company.
They cut his head off because of him.
To get him to talk.
They tortured Elyas
round-the-clock for a month.
He didn't tell them a thing.
The army got rid of him
and he was sent to a psych ward.
Then. when he got out.
he cut himself off from the world.
He was still there. but not really.
Like a broken-down machine.
And you guys...
You got him up and running again.
Elyas isn't a soldier.
He's a warrior.
Where's Yann? He's not picking up.
The whole thing stinks.
- What's going on. Elyas?
- No idea.
- You got guns here?
- Yeah.
- What have you got?
- Everything you need.
I'm gonna jump.
Where?
Here.
Afghanistan. Algeria.
Mauritania. Mali...
24 infiltration missions.
11 Jihadi chiefs eliminated. solo...
Specialist in extraction
and parachuting.
Tell them he's dangerous
and he's coming!
The airstrip is 15 minutes
from your drop point.
I can't hang around for long.
I can stay there 30 minutes. max.
Any longer. I'll have to take off.
Gotta make it quick. Elyas.
I've uploaded the airstrip coordinates
to your GPS.
In and out in 40 mins max
if you want us to make it to Morocco.
Less than 30 seconds.
Depressurizing in 5. 4. 3. 2. 1...
- Elyas?
- Yeah.
- Are you alone?
- Yes!
Elyas. you're alive! It's really you!
You came for me.
Get dressed. quick.
Stay behind me.
Stay close.
Stay right behind me.
They've disabled the elevator.
- Where are we going?
- The roof.
There's only one way up.
Through my dad's penthouse.
- Where?
- On the right. as you go out.
Climb on my back.
- There they are!
- On your right!
Take the keycard.
Get the door!
There's a service elevator
right at the end.
Look out! There!
Up ahead!
Cover your ears.
Get down.
This goes to the airlock.
then there's a corridor
to my dad's penthouse.
With me.
Wait in the elevator.
Wait inside.
Watch out. grenade!
Climb on my back.
Get away! Get away!
Get away!
Elyas. stop!
Stop!
Please. just stop!
Put it down. put it down.
Elyas...
Don't look.
Which way now?
My dad's penthouse.
From there. we can reach the roof.
Don't make any sound.
Come on! Go quicker. please.
- Is that him? Your father?
- Yeah.
Why have you stopped?
What are you doing?
That's his room.
Don't. Elyas!
Leave my dad. I just want to go.
Elyas. please!
You came for me. right?
You came to get me.
You're all I have left now.
Come on. let's go.
Let's go.
You're all I have left.
Here!
Here it is!
Okay. come on.
We'll jump together.
No way!
Elyas. you know I'm scared of heights.
You're giving up?
I won't drop you.
One foot in here.
Now your arm.
Your aunt's home is beautiful.
Mom would've loved it here.
I wasn't able to protect her.
Please forgive me.
Aunt Aicha!
Who is it?
Elyas.
- All done? You're enrolled?
- All done!
Meet Nour.
Nour and Boomer.
You already know Boomer.
He's your brother.
He's sleeping!
It's online.
I tagged the news outlets
and I sent it directly to the editors.
Wait.
See? Not so far. even by foot.
Got your enrollment letter?
Yeah.
Best get going.
- What if one of the teachers is mean?
- Only if you steal their cigs.
But what if I don't like school?
What if I get bored?
You'll never be bored.
Want to live like everyone else?
Choose your own future?
Decide for yourself?
Then it all starts here.
You'll be late.
You'll pick me up later?
Subtitles: Chris Smith
Pulse Translations
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm